<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Thirty days</string>
    <string name="title_day">Day %d</string>
    <string name="recipe1">Spaghetti Carbonara</string>
    <string name="description1">Classic Italian pasta dish with creamy sauce made from eggs, cheese, pancetta, and black pepper.</string>
    <string name="recipe2">Chicken Tikka Masala</string>
    <string name="description2">Tender chicken pieces marinated in yogurt and spices, then cooked in a creamy tomato sauce, popular in Indian cuisine.</string>
    <string name="recipe3">Beef Stroganoff</string>
    <string name="description3">Russian dish featuring tender strips of beef cooked with onions, mushrooms, and sour cream, served over noodles or rice </string>
    <string name="recipe4">Vegetable Stir-Fry</string>
    <string name="description4">Quick and healthy dish made by stir-frying a mix of colorful vegetables with soy sauce and other seasonings. </string>
    <string name="recipe5">Caprese Salad</string>
    <string name="description5">Simple Italian salad made with fresh tomatoes, mozzarella cheese, basil leaves, olive oil, and balsamic vinegar.</string>
    <string name="recipe6">Pad Thai</string>
    <string name="description6">Thai street food favorite made with stir-fried rice noodles, tofu or shrimp, bean sprouts, peanuts, and a tangy sauce.</string>
    <string name="recipe7">Beef Chili</string>
    <string name="description7">Hearty and spicy stew made with ground beef, beans, tomatoes, and chili peppers, perfect for a cozy night in.</string>
    <string name="recipe8">Mushroom Risotto</string>
    <string name="description8">Creamy Italian rice dish cooked with Arborio rice, mushrooms, onions, white wine, and Parmesan cheese.</string>
    <string name="recipe9">Sushi Rolls</string>
    <string name="description9">Homemade sushi rolls filled with ingredients like fresh fish, avocado, cucumber, and crab meat, wrapped in nori seaweed and sushi rice.</string>
    <string name="recipe10">Grilled Salmon</string>
    <string name="description10">Healthy and delicious salmon fillets marinated in a mix of lemon juice, garlic, and herbs, then grilled to perfection.</string>
    <string name="recipe11">Chicken Curry</string>
    <string name="description11">Flavorful Indian curry made with chicken pieces simmered in a rich sauce of tomatoes, onions, garlic, ginger, and spices.</string>
    <string name="recipe12">Guacamole</string>
    <string name="description12">Classic Mexican dip made with ripe avocados, tomatoes, onions, lime juice, cilantro, and jalapeños, served with tortilla chips.</string>
    <string name="recipe13">Beef Tacos</string>
    <string name="description13">Tasty Mexican street food made with seasoned ground beef, served in corn tortillas and topped with lettuce, cheese, salsa, and sour cream.</string>
    <string name="recipe14">Lemon Garlic Shrimp Pasta</string>
    <string name="description14">Quick and easy pasta dish featuring shrimp cooked in a lemon garlic butter sauce, served over linguine or spaghetti.</string>
    <string name="recipe15">Chicken Parmesan</string>
    <string name="description15">Crispy breaded chicken breasts topped with marinara sauce and melted mozzarella cheese, served with pasta.</string>
    <string name="recipe16">Tom Yum Soup</string>
    <string name="description16">Spicy and sour Thai soup made with shrimp or chicken, mushrooms, lemongrass, lime leaves, and chili peppers.</string>
    <string name="recipe17">Vegetable Lasagna</string>
    <string name="description17">Layers of lasagna noodles, marinara sauce, sautéed vegetables, ricotta cheese, and mozzarella cheese, baked to perfection.</string>
    <string name="recipe18">Beef Bulgogi</string>
    <string name="description18">Korean barbecue dish made with thinly sliced beef marinated in a sweet and savory sauce, then grilled or stir-fried.</string>
    <string name="recipe19">Ratatouille</string>
    <string name="description19">Classic French Provencal stewed vegetable dish made with eggplant, zucchini, bell peppers, onions, tomatoes, and herbs.</string>
    <string name="recipe20">Pesto Pasta</string>
    <string name="description20">Simple yet flavorful pasta dish made with spaghetti or penne tossed in a sauce made from fresh basil, garlic, pine nuts, Parmesan cheese, and olive oil.</string>
    <string name="recipe21">Honey Soy Glazed Chicken</string>
    <string name="description21">Tender chicken thighs marinated in a mixture of honey, soy sauce, garlic, and ginger, then baked or grilled until caramelized.</string>
    <string name="recipe22">Shakshuka</string>
    <string name="description22">Middle Eastern dish of poached eggs in a spicy tomato and pepper sauce, typically served with crusty bread for dipping.</string>
    <string name="recipe23">Beef Pho</string>
    <string name="description23">Vietnamese noodle soup made with beef broth, rice noodles, thinly sliced beef, and an assortment of fresh herbs and condiments.</string>
    <string name="recipe24">Falafel</string>
    <string name="description24">Middle Eastern street food made from ground chickpeas or fava beans, seasoned with herbs and spices, formed into balls, and deep-fried.</string>
    <string name="recipe25">Beef Wellington</string>
    <string name="description25">Elegant British dish featuring tender beef fillet coated with pâté and mushroom duxelles, wrapped in puff pastry and baked until golden brown.</string>
    <string name="recipe26">Pumpkin Soup</string>
    <string name="description26">Comforting soup made with roasted pumpkin, onions, garlic, broth, and cream, seasoned with herbs and spices.</string>
    <string name="recipe27">Chicken Shawarma</string>
    <string name="description27">Middle Eastern street food made with marinated chicken, roasted on a spit, and served with pita bread, tahini sauce, and pickled vegetables.</string>
    <string name="recipe28">Eggplant Parmesan</string>
    <string name="description28">Layers of breaded and fried eggplant slices topped with marinara sauce and melted mozzarella cheese, baked until bubbly.</string>
    <string name="recipe29">Ceviche</string>
    <string name="description29">Refreshing Latin American dish made with raw fish or seafood marinated in citrus juices, typically served with onions, cilantro, and chili peppers.</string>
    <string name="recipe30">Chicken Noodle Soup</string>
    <string name="description30">Classic comfort food made with chicken, vegetables, noodles, and broth, perfect for warming up on a chilly day.</string>
</resources>